[{"created_at":1752285691536,"content":"<p>Trump visits Texas flood disaster: 120 dead, 160 missing.<\/p><p><a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/casualties\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>casualties<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/Floodvictims\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>Floodvictims<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/texas\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>texas<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/trump\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>trump<\/span><\/a> <br \/><a href=\"https:\/\/blazetrends.com\/trump-visits-texas-flood-disaster-120-dead-160-missing\/?fsp_sid=65817\" target=\"_blank\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">blazetrends.com\/trump-visits-t<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">exas-flood-disaster-120-dead-160-missing\/?fsp_sid=65817<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"blazetrends","url":"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/@blazetrends\/114837795080180808","clean_content":"Trump visits Texas flood disaster: 120 dead, 160 missing. #casualties #flood #Floodvictims #texas #trump https:\/\/ blazetrends.com\/trump-visits-t exas-flood-disaster-120-dead-160-missing\/?fsp_sid=65817","hashtags":["casualties","flood","Floodvictims","texas","trump"],"entities":[["Trump","ORG"],["Texas","GPE"],["120","CARDINAL"],["160","CARDINAL"],["#","CARDINAL"],["#","CARDINAL"]],"keywords":["href","tag","hashtag","tags","missing"],"cluster":3,"sentiment":-0.2,"topic_id":3,"topic_label":"texas, fema, calls, floods, trump"},{"created_at":1752285618000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NWS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NWS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/nwsflashflood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>nwsflashflood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FlashFloodWarning\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FlashFloodWarning<\/span><\/a> Flash Flood Warning for Hancock, IL; McDonough, IL; Warren, IL; Clark, MO <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/MOwx\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>MOwx<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?id=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.6bd315b4525787bbe1949ea258aba118f0c341d9.001.1\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.6bd315b4525787bbe1949ea258aba118f0c341d9.001.1<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"flashflood_bot","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@flashflood_bot\/114837790315795364","clean_content":"#NWS #flood #nwsflashflood #FlashFloodWarning Flash Flood Warning for Hancock, IL; McDonough, IL; Warren, IL; Clark, MO #MOwx https:\/\/ alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.6bd315b4525787bbe1949ea258aba118f0c341d9.001.1","hashtags":["NWS","flood","nwsflashflood","FlashFloodWarning","MOwx"],"entities":[["NWS","ORG"],["#","CARDINAL"],["Flash Flood Warning","PERSON"],["IL","ORG"],["McDonough","ORG"],["IL","ORG"],["Warren","GPE"],["IL","ORG"],["Clark","GPE"],["MO","GPE"],["MOwx","PERSON"],["oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.6bd315b4525787bbe1949ea258aba118f0c341d9.001.1","PERSON"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","nofollow","tags","noopener"],"cluster":4,"sentiment":0.0,"topic_id":0,"topic_label":"flood, 49, alerts, gov, flashfloodwarning"},{"created_at":1752285377000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/EAS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>EAS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/WEA\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>WEA<\/span><\/a> for Hancock, <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/IL\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>IL<\/span><\/a>; <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/McDonough\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>McDonough<\/span><\/a>, <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/IL\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>IL<\/span><\/a>; <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/Warren\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>Warren<\/span><\/a>, <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/IL\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>IL<\/span><\/a>; <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/Clark\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>Clark<\/span><\/a>, <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/MO\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>MO<\/span><\/a>: National Weather Service: A FLASH <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FLOOD\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FLOOD<\/span><\/a> WARNING is in effect for this area until 3:00 AM CDT. This is a dangerous and life-threatening situation. Do not attempt to travel unless you are fleeing an area subject to flooding or under an evacuation order. Source: NWS Quad Cities IA IL ** DO NOT RELY ON THIS FEED FOR LIFE SAFETY, SEEK OUT OFFICIAL SOURCES ***<\/p>","username":"easwatch","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@easwatch\/114837774478144627","clean_content":"#EAS #WEA for Hancock, #IL ; #McDonough , #IL ; #Warren , #IL ; #Clark , #MO : National Weather Service: A FLASH #FLOOD WARNING is in effect for this area until 3:00 AM CDT. This is a dangerous and life-threatening situation. Do not attempt to travel unless you are fleeing an area subject to flooding or under an evacuation order. Source: NWS Quad Cities IA IL ** DO NOT RELY ON THIS FEED FOR LIFE SAFETY, SEEK OUT OFFICIAL SOURCES ***","hashtags":["EAS","WEA","IL","McDonough","IL","Warren","IL","Clark","MO","FLOOD"],"entities":[["#EAS #","MONEY"],["WEA","ORG"],["IL","PERSON"],["McDonough","PERSON"],["IL","PERSON"],["Warren","PERSON"],["IL","PERSON"],["Clark","PERSON"],["MO","PERSON"],["National Weather Service","ORG"],["3:00 AM CDT","TIME"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","tags","nofollow","hancock"],"cluster":1,"sentiment":-0.3833333333,"topic_id":1,"topic_label":"il, ia, life, area, feed"},{"created_at":1752285129000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NWS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NWS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/nwsflashflood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>nwsflashflood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FlashFloodWarning\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FlashFloodWarning<\/span><\/a> Flash Flood Warning for Clinton, IA; Scott, IA; Carroll, IL; Rock Island, IL; Whiteside, IL <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/ILwx\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>ILwx<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?id=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.0c4ec8a1182c18decbae4dad0927412fc2608859.001.1\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.0c4ec8a1182c18decbae4dad0927412fc2608859.001.1<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"flashflood_bot","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@flashflood_bot\/114837758277096603","clean_content":"#NWS #flood #nwsflashflood #FlashFloodWarning Flash Flood Warning for Clinton, IA; Scott, IA; Carroll, IL; Rock Island, IL; Whiteside, IL #ILwx https:\/\/ alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.0c4ec8a1182c18decbae4dad0927412fc2608859.001.1","hashtags":["NWS","flood","nwsflashflood","FlashFloodWarning","ILwx"],"entities":[["NWS","ORG"],["#","CARDINAL"],["Flash Flood Warning","PERSON"],["Clinton","PERSON"],["IA","GPE"],["Scott","ORG"],["IA","GPE"],["Carroll","GPE"],["IL","ORG"],["Rock Island","GPE"],["IL","ORG"],["Whiteside","ORG"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","nofollow","tags","noopener"],"cluster":4,"sentiment":0.0,"topic_id":0,"topic_label":"flood, 49, alerts, gov, flashfloodwarning"},{"created_at":1752284173000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NWS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NWS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/nwsflashflood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>nwsflashflood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FlashFloodWarning\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FlashFloodWarning<\/span><\/a> Flash Flood Warning for Des Moines, IA; Henry, IA; Lee, IA; Van Buren, IA; Hancock, IL; Henderson, IL; McDonough, IL; Warren, IL; Clark, MO; Scotland, MO <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/MOwx\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>MOwx<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?id=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.8ca37c2769cbabec528945ea64810357fa470fb1.001.1\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.8ca37c2769cbabec528945ea64810357fa470fb1.001.1<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"flashflood_bot","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@flashflood_bot\/114837695578693340","clean_content":"#NWS #flood #nwsflashflood #FlashFloodWarning Flash Flood Warning for Des Moines, IA; Henry, IA; Lee, IA; Van Buren, IA; Hancock, IL; Henderson, IL; McDonough, IL; Warren, IL; Clark, MO; Scotland, MO #MOwx https:\/\/ alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.8ca37c2769cbabec528945ea64810357fa470fb1.001.1","hashtags":["NWS","flood","nwsflashflood","FlashFloodWarning","MOwx"],"entities":[["NWS","ORG"],["#","CARDINAL"],["Flash Flood Warning","PERSON"],["Des Moines","GPE"],["IA","GPE"],["Henry","GPE"],["IA","GPE"],["Lee","PERSON"],["IA","GPE"],["Van Buren","PERSON"],["IA","GPE"],["Hancock","GPE"],["IL","ORG"],["Henderson","GPE"],["IL","ORG"],["McDonough","ORG"],["IL","ORG"],["Warren","GPE"],["IL","ORG"],["Clark","PERSON"],["MO","GPE"],["Scotland","GPE"],["MO","GPE"],["MOwx","PERSON"],["oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.8ca37c2769cbabec528945ea64810357fa470fb1.001.1","PERSON"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","nofollow","tags","noopener"],"cluster":4,"sentiment":0.0,"topic_id":1,"topic_label":"il, ia, life, area, feed"},{"created_at":1752284074000,"content":"<p>Consequences of <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/Firing\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>Firing<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/mission\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>mission<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/critical\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>critical<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/government\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>government<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/employees\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>employees<\/span><\/a> &amp; <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/contractors\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>contractors<\/span><\/a> - <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/FEMA\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FEMA<\/span><\/a> Didn’t Answer Thousands of Calls From Flood Survivors, Documents Show. Two days after deadly <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/Texas\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>Texas<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/floods\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>floods<\/span><\/a>, the agency struggled to answer calls from <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/survivors\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>survivors<\/span><\/a> because of <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/callcenter\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>callcenter<\/span><\/a> contracts that weren’t extended. <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/maga\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>maga<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/trump\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>trump<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/gop\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>gop<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/congress\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>congress<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/republicans\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>republicans<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/government\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>government<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/disasters\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>disasters<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/flooding\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flooding<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/texas\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>texas<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/trump\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>trump<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/jdvance\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>jdvance<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/KristiNoem\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>KristiNoem<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/homelandsecurity\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>homelandsecurity<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/DHS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>DHS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/failed\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>failed<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/searchandrescue\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>searchandrescue<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/www.nytimes.com\/2025\/07\/11\/climate\/fema-missed-calls-texas-floods.html\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/www.<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">nytimes.com\/2025\/07\/11\/climate<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">\/fema-missed-calls-texas-floods.html<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"bespacific","url":"https:\/\/newsie.social\/@bespacific\/114837689109535270","clean_content":"Consequences of #Firing #mission #critical #government #employees & #contractors - #FEMA Didn’t Answer Thousands of Calls From Flood Survivors, Documents Show. Two days after deadly #Texas #floods , the agency struggled to answer calls from #survivors because of #callcenter contracts that weren’t extended. #maga #trump #gop #congress #republicans #government #disasters #flood #flooding #texas #trump #jdvance #KristiNoem #homelandsecurity #DHS #failed #searchandrescue https:\/\/www. nytimes.com\/2025\/07\/11\/climate \/fema-missed-calls-texas-floods.html","hashtags":["Firing","mission","critical","government","employees","contractors","FEMA","Texas","floods","survivors","callcenter","maga","trump","gop","congress","republicans","government","disasters","flood","flooding","texas","trump","jdvance","KristiNoem","homelandsecurity","DHS","failed","searchandrescue"],"entities":[["#Firing #","MONEY"],["#","CARDINAL"],["#","CARDINAL"],["FEMA","ORG"],["Two days","DATE"],["#","CARDINAL"],["Texas","PERSON"],["#","CARDINAL"],["#","CARDINAL"],["maga","PERSON"],["#","CARDINAL"],["#","CARDINAL"],["gop","ORG"],["#","CARDINAL"],["#","CARDINAL"],["#","CARDINAL"],["KristiNoem","ORG"],["#","CARDINAL"],["texas","GPE"]],"keywords":["href","nofollow","hashtag","html","tags"],"cluster":3,"sentiment":-0.2333333333,"topic_id":3,"topic_label":"texas, fema, calls, floods, trump"},{"created_at":1752283706000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NWS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NWS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/nwsflashflood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>nwsflashflood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FlashFloodWarning\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FlashFloodWarning<\/span><\/a> Flash Flood Warning for Morgan, CO; Weld, CO <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/COwx\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>COwx<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?id=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.894ce899bdfbd4ce5411b7403b4ba13dae94525f.001.1\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.894ce899bdfbd4ce5411b7403b4ba13dae94525f.001.1<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"flashflood_bot","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@flashflood_bot\/114837664997933672","clean_content":"#NWS #flood #nwsflashflood #FlashFloodWarning Flash Flood Warning for Morgan, CO; Weld, CO #COwx https:\/\/ alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.894ce899bdfbd4ce5411b7403b4ba13dae94525f.001.1","hashtags":["NWS","flood","nwsflashflood","FlashFloodWarning","COwx"],"entities":[["NWS","ORG"],["#","CARDINAL"],["Flash Flood Warning","PERSON"],["Morgan","PERSON"],["CO","ORG"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","nofollow","tags","noopener"],"cluster":0,"sentiment":0.0,"topic_id":0,"topic_label":"flood, 49, alerts, gov, flashfloodwarning"},{"created_at":1752283700000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NWS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NWS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/nwsflashflood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>nwsflashflood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FlashFloodWarning\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FlashFloodWarning<\/span><\/a> Flash Flood Warning for Otero, CO; Pueblo, CO <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/COwx\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>COwx<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?id=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.e535a6ceb091e33c5090892c479bf5c9efd6c421.001.1\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.e535a6ceb091e33c5090892c479bf5c9efd6c421.001.1<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"flashflood_bot","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@flashflood_bot\/114837664621771150","clean_content":"#NWS #flood #nwsflashflood #FlashFloodWarning Flash Flood Warning for Otero, CO; Pueblo, CO #COwx https:\/\/ alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.e535a6ceb091e33c5090892c479bf5c9efd6c421.001.1","hashtags":["NWS","flood","nwsflashflood","FlashFloodWarning","COwx"],"entities":[["NWS","ORG"],["#","CARDINAL"],["Flash Flood Warning","PERSON"],["Otero","PERSON"],["CO","ORG"],["Pueblo, CO #COwx","ORG"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","nofollow","tags","noopener"],"cluster":0,"sentiment":0.0,"topic_id":0,"topic_label":"flood, 49, alerts, gov, flashfloodwarning"},{"created_at":1752283696000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/EAS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>EAS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/WEA\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>WEA<\/span><\/a> for Des Moines, <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/IA\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>IA<\/span><\/a>; <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/Henry\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>Henry<\/span><\/a>, <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/IA\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>IA<\/span><\/a>; <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/Lee\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>Lee<\/span><\/a>, <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/IA\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>IA<\/span><\/a>; <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/Van\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>Van<\/span><\/a> Buren, <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/IA\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>IA<\/span><\/a>; <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/Hancock\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>Hancock<\/span><\/a>, <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/IL\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>IL<\/span><\/a>; <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/Henderson\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>Henderson<\/span><\/a>, <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/IL\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>IL<\/span><\/a>; <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/McDonough\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>McDonough<\/span><\/a>, <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/IL\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>IL<\/span><\/a>; <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/Warren\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>Warren<\/span><\/a>, <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/IL\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>IL<\/span><\/a>; <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/Clark\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>Clark<\/span><\/a>, <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/MO\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>MO<\/span><\/a>; <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/Scotland\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>Scotland<\/span><\/a>, <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/MO\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>MO<\/span><\/a>: National Weather Service: A FLASH <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FLOOD\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FLOOD<\/span><\/a> WARNING is in effect for this area until 2:30 AM CDT. This is a dangerous and life-threatening situation. Do not attempt to travel unless you are fleeing an area subject to flooding or under an evacuation order. Source: NWS Quad Cities IA IL ** DO NOT RELY ON THIS FEED FOR LIFE SAFETY, SEEK OU<\/p>","username":"easwatch","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@easwatch\/114837664322321279","clean_content":"#EAS #WEA for Des Moines, #IA ; #Henry , #IA ; #Lee , #IA ; #Van Buren, #IA ; #Hancock , #IL ; #Henderson , #IL ; #McDonough , #IL ; #Warren , #IL ; #Clark , #MO ; #Scotland , #MO : National Weather Service: A FLASH #FLOOD WARNING is in effect for this area until 2:30 AM CDT. This is a dangerous and life-threatening situation. Do not attempt to travel unless you are fleeing an area subject to flooding or under an evacuation order. Source: NWS Quad Cities IA IL ** DO NOT RELY ON THIS FEED FOR LIFE SAFETY, SEEK OU","hashtags":["EAS","WEA","IA","Henry","IA","Lee","IA","Van","IA","Hancock","IL","Henderson","IL","McDonough","IL","Warren","IL","Clark","MO","Scotland","MO","FLOOD"],"entities":[["#EAS #","MONEY"],["WEA","ORG"],["Des Moines","GPE"],["IA","GPE"],["Henry","PERSON"],["Lee","PERSON"],["Van Buren","PERSON"],["Hancock","PERSON"],["IL","PERSON"],["Henderson","PERSON"],["IL","PERSON"],["McDonough","PERSON"],["IL","PERSON"],["Warren","PERSON"],["IL","PERSON"],["Clark","PERSON"],["MO","GPE"],["Scotland","GPE"],["MO","PERSON"],["National Weather Service","ORG"],["2:30 AM CDT","TIME"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","tags","nofollow","moines"],"cluster":1,"sentiment":-0.3833333333,"topic_id":1,"topic_label":"il, ia, life, area, feed"},{"created_at":1752283694000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NWS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NWS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/nwsflashflood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>nwsflashflood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FlashFloodWarning\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FlashFloodWarning<\/span><\/a> Flash Flood Warning for Des Moines, IA; Henry, IA; Louisa, IA; Muscatine, IA; Henderson, IL; Mercer, IL; Rock Island, IL <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/ILwx\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>ILwx<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?id=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.7d3615164292d5d46fe9d7c32f728bc9b51c19f0.001.1\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.7d3615164292d5d46fe9d7c32f728bc9b51c19f0.001.1<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"flashflood_bot","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@flashflood_bot\/114837664189868873","clean_content":"#NWS #flood #nwsflashflood #FlashFloodWarning Flash Flood Warning for Des Moines, IA; Henry, IA; Louisa, IA; Muscatine, IA; Henderson, IL; Mercer, IL; Rock Island, IL #ILwx https:\/\/ alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.7d3615164292d5d46fe9d7c32f728bc9b51c19f0.001.1","hashtags":["NWS","flood","nwsflashflood","FlashFloodWarning","ILwx"],"entities":[["NWS","ORG"],["#","CARDINAL"],["Flash Flood Warning","PERSON"],["Des Moines","GPE"],["IA","GPE"],["Henry","GPE"],["IA","GPE"],["Louisa","GPE"],["IA","GPE"],["Muscatine","ORG"],["IA","GPE"],["Henderson","GPE"],["IL","ORG"],["Mercer","PERSON"],["IL","ORG"],["Rock Island","GPE"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","nofollow","tags","noopener"],"cluster":4,"sentiment":0.0,"topic_id":0,"topic_label":"flood, 49, alerts, gov, flashfloodwarning"},{"created_at":1752282731000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NWS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NWS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/nwsflashflood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>nwsflashflood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FlashFloodWarning\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FlashFloodWarning<\/span><\/a> Flash Flood Warning for Luna, NM <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NMwx\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NMwx<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?id=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.d8a00c84f67453121e42e3d80ec5a873dbe36412.001.1\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.d8a00c84f67453121e42e3d80ec5a873dbe36412.001.1<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"flashflood_bot","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@flashflood_bot\/114837601077861781","clean_content":"#NWS #flood #nwsflashflood #FlashFloodWarning Flash Flood Warning for Luna, NM #NMwx https:\/\/ alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.d8a00c84f67453121e42e3d80ec5a873dbe36412.001.1","hashtags":["NWS","flood","nwsflashflood","FlashFloodWarning","NMwx"],"entities":[["NWS","ORG"],["#","CARDINAL"],["Flash Flood Warning","PERSON"],["NMwx","PERSON"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","nofollow","tags","noopener"],"cluster":0,"sentiment":0.0,"topic_id":0,"topic_label":"flood, 49, alerts, gov, flashfloodwarning"},{"created_at":1752281770000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NWS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NWS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/nwsflashflood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>nwsflashflood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FlashFloodWarning\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FlashFloodWarning<\/span><\/a> Flash Flood Warning for Bureau, IL; Putnam, IL <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/ILwx\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>ILwx<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?id=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.40f0c1c6199849ebb9bd28921ef7203b3af33fe5.001.1\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.40f0c1c6199849ebb9bd28921ef7203b3af33fe5.001.1<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"flashflood_bot","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@flashflood_bot\/114837538131980720","clean_content":"#NWS #flood #nwsflashflood #FlashFloodWarning Flash Flood Warning for Bureau, IL; Putnam, IL #ILwx https:\/\/ alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.40f0c1c6199849ebb9bd28921ef7203b3af33fe5.001.1","hashtags":["NWS","flood","nwsflashflood","FlashFloodWarning","ILwx"],"entities":[["NWS","ORG"],["#","CARDINAL"],["Flash Flood Warning for Bureau","PERSON"],["IL","ORG"],["Putnam","GPE"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","nofollow","tags","noopener"],"cluster":4,"sentiment":0.0,"topic_id":0,"topic_label":"flood, 49, alerts, gov, flashfloodwarning"},{"created_at":1752281367163,"content":"<p>Experts been warning us about purple ocean but does not explain why. With the collapse, reversal and warming of the ocean, the polar excursion is culprit. The oceans will become darker soon. <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/poleshift\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>poleshift<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/polarexcursion\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>polarexcursion<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/earthtilt\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>earthtilt<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/cataclysm\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>cataclysm<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/disaster\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>disaster<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/fire\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>fire<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/tornado\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>tornado<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"poleshiftbot","url":"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/@poleshiftbot\/114837511678030569","clean_content":"Experts been warning us about purple ocean but does not explain why. With the collapse, reversal and warming of the ocean, the polar excursion is culprit. The oceans will become darker soon. #poleshift #polarexcursion #earthtilt #cataclysm #disaster #flood #fire #tornado","hashtags":["poleshift","polarexcursion","earthtilt","cataclysm","disaster","flood","fire","tornado"],"entities":[["#","CARDINAL"],["#","CARDINAL"],["cataclysm","PERSON"],["#","CARDINAL"]],"keywords":["oceans","polar","ocean","polarexcursion","href"],"cluster":2,"sentiment":-0.0833333333,"topic_id":4,"topic_label":"tornado, poleshift, polarexcursion, earthtilt, cataclysm"},{"created_at":1752281291000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NWS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NWS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/nwsflashflood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>nwsflashflood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FlashFloodWarning\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FlashFloodWarning<\/span><\/a> Flash Flood Warning for Scott, IA; Rock Island, IL <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/ILwx\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>ILwx<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?id=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.25681536540c93b1d58b0d3cc5a15be81976e9a4.001.1\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.25681536540c93b1d58b0d3cc5a15be81976e9a4.001.1<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"flashflood_bot","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@flashflood_bot\/114837506751127536","clean_content":"#NWS #flood #nwsflashflood #FlashFloodWarning Flash Flood Warning for Scott, IA; Rock Island, IL #ILwx https:\/\/ alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.25681536540c93b1d58b0d3cc5a15be81976e9a4.001.1","hashtags":["NWS","flood","nwsflashflood","FlashFloodWarning","ILwx"],"entities":[["NWS","ORG"],["#","CARDINAL"],["Flash Flood Warning","PERSON"],["Scott","ORG"],["IA","GPE"],["Rock Island","GPE"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","nofollow","tags","noopener"],"cluster":4,"sentiment":0.0,"topic_id":0,"topic_label":"flood, 49, alerts, gov, flashfloodwarning"},{"created_at":1752281055000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/EAS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>EAS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/WEA\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>WEA<\/span><\/a> for Scott, <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/IA\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>IA<\/span><\/a>; <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/Rock\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>Rock<\/span><\/a> Island, <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/IL\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>IL<\/span><\/a>: National Weather Service: A FLASH <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FLOOD\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FLOOD<\/span><\/a> EMERGENCY is in effect for this area until 4:00 AM CDT. This is an extremely dangerous and life-threatening situation. Do not attempt to travel unless you are fleeing an area subject to flooding or under an evacuation order. Source: NWS Quad Cities IA IL ** DO NOT RELY ON THIS FEED FOR LIFE SAFETY, SEEK OUT OFFICIAL SOURCES ***<\/p>","username":"easwatch","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@easwatch\/114837491259739572","clean_content":"#EAS #WEA for Scott, #IA ; #Rock Island, #IL : National Weather Service: A FLASH #FLOOD EMERGENCY is in effect for this area until 4:00 AM CDT. This is an extremely dangerous and life-threatening situation. Do not attempt to travel unless you are fleeing an area subject to flooding or under an evacuation order. Source: NWS Quad Cities IA IL ** DO NOT RELY ON THIS FEED FOR LIFE SAFETY, SEEK OUT OFFICIAL SOURCES ***","hashtags":["EAS","WEA","IA","Rock","IL","FLOOD"],"entities":[["#EAS #","MONEY"],["WEA","ORG"],["Scott","ORG"],["IA","GPE"],["Rock Island","PERSON"],["IL","PERSON"],["4:00 AM CDT","TIME"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","tags","nofollow","scott"],"cluster":1,"sentiment":-0.3833333333,"topic_id":1,"topic_label":"il, ia, life, area, feed"},{"created_at":1752280828000,"content":"<p>\"Noem’s insistence on approving expenses over $100,000 had also delayed FEMA’s deployment of search-and-rescue teams to Texas... Noem did not authorize the deployment of those teams until July 7, three days after the <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/flooding\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flooding<\/span><\/a> began...<\/p><p>Richardson [FEMA’s acting administrator] ... has no background in emergency management...<\/p><p><a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/Trump\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>Trump<\/span><\/a> has talked of eliminating <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/FEMA\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FEMA<\/span><\/a>\"<\/p><p><a href=\"https:\/\/www.nytimes.com\/2025\/07\/11\/climate\/fema-missed-calls-texas-floods.html\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/www.<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">nytimes.com\/2025\/07\/11\/climate<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">\/fema-missed-calls-texas-floods.html<\/span><\/a><\/p><p><a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/KristiNoem\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>KristiNoem<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/USPol\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>USPol<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/Politics\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>Politics<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/Flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>Flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/Texas\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>Texas<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/TexasFloods\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>TexasFloods<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/FEMA\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FEMA<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/News\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>News<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/Press\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>Press<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/US\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>US<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/USA\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>USA<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"ZhiZhu","url":"https:\/\/newsie.social\/@ZhiZhu\/114837476362172123","clean_content":"\"Noem’s insistence on approving expenses over $100,000 had also delayed FEMA’s deployment of search-and-rescue teams to Texas... Noem did not authorize the deployment of those teams until July 7, three days after the #flooding began... Richardson [FEMA’s acting administrator] ... has no background in emergency management... #Trump has talked of eliminating #FEMA \" https:\/\/www. nytimes.com\/2025\/07\/11\/climate \/fema-missed-calls-texas-floods.html #KristiNoem #USPol #Politics #Flood #Texas #TexasFloods #FEMA #News #Press #US #USA","hashtags":["flooding","Trump","FEMA","KristiNoem","USPol","Politics","Flood","Texas","TexasFloods","FEMA","News","Press","US","USA"],"entities":[["Noem","ORG"],["over $100,000","MONEY"],["FEMA","ORG"],["Texas","GPE"],["Noem","PERSON"],["July 7","DATE"],["three days","DATE"],["Richardson","PERSON"],["FEMA","ORG"],["Trump","PERSON"],["FEMA","ORG"],["#KristiNoem #","MONEY"],["USPol","PERSON"],["#Flood #","MONEY"],["FEMA","ORG"]],"keywords":["fema","nofollow","richardson","rescue","hashtag"],"cluster":3,"sentiment":0.0,"topic_id":3,"topic_label":"texas, fema, calls, floods, trump"},{"created_at":1752280812000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NWS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NWS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/nwsflashflood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>nwsflashflood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FlashFloodWarning\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FlashFloodWarning<\/span><\/a> Flash Flood Warning for Colfax, NM <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NMwx\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NMwx<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?id=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.0f9f35aeaa251b09c606d8d70d7be579aaa24fb6.001.1\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.0f9f35aeaa251b09c606d8d70d7be579aaa24fb6.001.1<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"flashflood_bot","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@flashflood_bot\/114837475314521704","clean_content":"#NWS #flood #nwsflashflood #FlashFloodWarning Flash Flood Warning for Colfax, NM #NMwx https:\/\/ alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.0f9f35aeaa251b09c606d8d70d7be579aaa24fb6.001.1","hashtags":["NWS","flood","nwsflashflood","FlashFloodWarning","NMwx"],"entities":[["NWS","ORG"],["#","CARDINAL"],["Flash Flood Warning for","PERSON"],["NMwx","PERSON"],["oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.0f9f35aeaa251b09c606d8d70d7be579aaa24fb6.001.1","PERSON"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","nofollow","tags","noopener"],"cluster":0,"sentiment":0.0,"topic_id":0,"topic_label":"flood, 49, alerts, gov, flashfloodwarning"},{"created_at":1752279743000,"content":"<p>\"On July 5, as floodwaters were starting to recede, <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/FEMA\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FEMA<\/span><\/a> received 3,027 calls from disaster survivors and answered 3,018, or roughly 99.7%...<\/p><p>That evening, however, Noem did not renew the contracts...<\/p><p>The next day, July 6, FEMA received 2,363 calls and answered 846, or roughly 35.8%, according to the documents. And on Monday, July 7, the agency fielded 16,419 calls and answered 2,613, or around 15.9%, the documents show.\"<br><a href=\"https:\/\/www.nytimes.com\/2025\/07\/11\/climate\/fema-missed-calls-texas-floods.html\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/www.<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">nytimes.com\/2025\/07\/11\/climate<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">\/fema-missed-calls-texas-floods.html<\/span><\/a><\/p><p><a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/Trump\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>Trump<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/GOP\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>GOP<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/USPol\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>USPol<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/Texas\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>Texas<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/Flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>Flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/News\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>News<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/newsie.social\/tags\/USA\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>USA<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"ZhiZhu","url":"https:\/\/newsie.social\/@ZhiZhu\/114837405263388326","clean_content":"\"On July 5, as floodwaters were starting to recede, #FEMA received 3,027 calls from disaster survivors and answered 3,018, or roughly 99.7%... That evening, however, Noem did not renew the contracts... The next day, July 6, FEMA received 2,363 calls and answered 846, or roughly 35.8%, according to the documents. And on Monday, July 7, the agency fielded 16,419 calls and answered 2,613, or around 15.9%, the documents show.\" https:\/\/www. nytimes.com\/2025\/07\/11\/climate \/fema-missed-calls-texas-floods.html #Trump #GOP #USPol #Texas #Flood #News #USA","hashtags":["FEMA","Trump","GOP","USPol","Texas","Flood","News","USA"],"entities":[["July 5","DATE"],["FEMA","ORG"],["3,027","CARDINAL"],["3,018","CARDINAL"],["roughly 99.7%","PERCENT"],["Noem","ORG"],["The next day","DATE"],["July 6","DATE"],["FEMA","ORG"],["2,363","CARDINAL"],["846","CARDINAL"],["roughly 35.8%","PERCENT"],["Monday, July 7","DATE"],["16,419","CARDINAL"],["2,613","CARDINAL"],["around 15.9%","PERCENT"],["Trump","PERSON"],["GOP","ORG"],["USPol","PERSON"]],"keywords":["fema","flood","floods","floodwaters","calls"],"cluster":3,"sentiment":-0.05,"topic_id":3,"topic_label":"texas, fema, calls, floods, trump"},{"created_at":1752279375000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NWS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NWS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/nwsflashflood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>nwsflashflood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FlashFloodWarning\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FlashFloodWarning<\/span><\/a> Flash Flood Warning for Benton, IA; Buchanan, IA; Delaware, IA; Linn, IA <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/IAwx\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>IAwx<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?id=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.8b5cf1181ee7ba7bc7d7c8085c0504aff442c5ca.001.1\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.8b5cf1181ee7ba7bc7d7c8085c0504aff442c5ca.001.1<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"flashflood_bot","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@flashflood_bot\/114837381183641089","clean_content":"#NWS #flood #nwsflashflood #FlashFloodWarning Flash Flood Warning for Benton, IA; Buchanan, IA; Delaware, IA; Linn, IA #IAwx https:\/\/ alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.8b5cf1181ee7ba7bc7d7c8085c0504aff442c5ca.001.1","hashtags":["NWS","flood","nwsflashflood","FlashFloodWarning","IAwx"],"entities":[["NWS","ORG"],["#","CARDINAL"],["Flash Flood Warning","PERSON"],["Benton","PERSON"],["IA","GPE"],["Buchanan","GPE"],["IA","GPE"],["Delaware","GPE"],["IA","GPE"],["Linn","PERSON"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","nofollow","tags","noopener"],"cluster":4,"sentiment":0.0,"topic_id":0,"topic_label":"flood, 49, alerts, gov, flashfloodwarning"},{"created_at":1752279369000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NWS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NWS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/nwsflashflood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>nwsflashflood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FlashFloodWarning\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FlashFloodWarning<\/span><\/a> Flash Flood Warning for Luna, NM <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NMwx\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NMwx<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?id=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.57d598f5e0cd7d3c3aa80cfcfd377ad6b1de504e.001.1\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.57d598f5e0cd7d3c3aa80cfcfd377ad6b1de504e.001.1<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"flashflood_bot","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@flashflood_bot\/114837380759031070","clean_content":"#NWS #flood #nwsflashflood #FlashFloodWarning Flash Flood Warning for Luna, NM #NMwx https:\/\/ alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.57d598f5e0cd7d3c3aa80cfcfd377ad6b1de504e.001.1","hashtags":["NWS","flood","nwsflashflood","FlashFloodWarning","NMwx"],"entities":[["NWS","ORG"],["#","CARDINAL"],["Flash Flood Warning","PERSON"],["NMwx","PERSON"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","nofollow","tags","noopener"],"cluster":0,"sentiment":0.0,"topic_id":0,"topic_label":"flood, 49, alerts, gov, flashfloodwarning"},{"created_at":1752278903000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NWS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NWS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/nwsflashflood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>nwsflashflood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FlashFloodWarning\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FlashFloodWarning<\/span><\/a> Flash Flood Warning for Clay, NC <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NCwx\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NCwx<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?id=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.0e23972df415fbc0f6b385f3568647b071ac1396.001.1\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.0e23972df415fbc0f6b385f3568647b071ac1396.001.1<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"flashflood_bot","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@flashflood_bot\/114837350190117846","clean_content":"#NWS #flood #nwsflashflood #FlashFloodWarning Flash Flood Warning for Clay, NC #NCwx https:\/\/ alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.0e23972df415fbc0f6b385f3568647b071ac1396.001.1","hashtags":["NWS","flood","nwsflashflood","FlashFloodWarning","NCwx"],"entities":[["NWS","ORG"],["#","CARDINAL"],["Flash Flood Warning for","PERSON"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","nofollow","tags","noopener"],"cluster":0,"sentiment":0.0,"topic_id":0,"topic_label":"flood, 49, alerts, gov, flashfloodwarning"},{"created_at":1752278898000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NWS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NWS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/nwsflashflood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>nwsflashflood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FlashFloodWarning\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FlashFloodWarning<\/span><\/a> Flash Flood Warning for Clinton, PA; Lycoming, PA; Union, PA <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/PAwx\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>PAwx<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?id=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.3be428174343139ab4baae46273d54a6226ddc54.001.1\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.3be428174343139ab4baae46273d54a6226ddc54.001.1<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"flashflood_bot","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@flashflood_bot\/114837349918795065","clean_content":"#NWS #flood #nwsflashflood #FlashFloodWarning Flash Flood Warning for Clinton, PA; Lycoming, PA; Union, PA #PAwx https:\/\/ alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.3be428174343139ab4baae46273d54a6226ddc54.001.1","hashtags":["NWS","flood","nwsflashflood","FlashFloodWarning","PAwx"],"entities":[["NWS","ORG"],["#","CARDINAL"],["Flash Flood Warning","PERSON"],["Clinton","PERSON"],["Lycoming","GPE"],["Union","GPE"],["PAwx","MONEY"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","nofollow","tags","noopener"],"cluster":0,"sentiment":0.0,"topic_id":0,"topic_label":"flood, 49, alerts, gov, flashfloodwarning"},{"created_at":1752277939000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NWS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NWS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/nwsflashflood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>nwsflashflood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FlashFloodWarning\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FlashFloodWarning<\/span><\/a> Flash Flood Warning for Scott, IA; Rock Island, IL <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/ILwx\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>ILwx<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?id=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.a3ed7786a98c65d631462a82bed4e0fd10f9df83.001.1\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.a3ed7786a98c65d631462a82bed4e0fd10f9df83.001.1<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"flashflood_bot","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@flashflood_bot\/114837287068968178","clean_content":"#NWS #flood #nwsflashflood #FlashFloodWarning Flash Flood Warning for Scott, IA; Rock Island, IL #ILwx https:\/\/ alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.a3ed7786a98c65d631462a82bed4e0fd10f9df83.001.1","hashtags":["NWS","flood","nwsflashflood","FlashFloodWarning","ILwx"],"entities":[["NWS","ORG"],["#","CARDINAL"],["Flash Flood Warning","PERSON"],["Scott","ORG"],["IA","GPE"],["Rock Island","GPE"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","nofollow","tags","noopener"],"cluster":4,"sentiment":0.0,"topic_id":0,"topic_label":"flood, 49, alerts, gov, flashfloodwarning"},{"created_at":1752277933000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NWS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NWS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/nwsflashflood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>nwsflashflood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FlashFloodWarning\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FlashFloodWarning<\/span><\/a> Flash Flood Warning for Dane, WI; Green, WI; Iowa, WI; Lafayette, WI <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/WIwx\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>WIwx<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?id=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.72a97c9be4a284482db6e5271cee6b3340ebd9d8.001.1\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.72a97c9be4a284482db6e5271cee6b3340ebd9d8.001.1<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"flashflood_bot","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@flashflood_bot\/114837286632827380","clean_content":"#NWS #flood #nwsflashflood #FlashFloodWarning Flash Flood Warning for Dane, WI; Green, WI; Iowa, WI; Lafayette, WI #WIwx https:\/\/ alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.72a97c9be4a284482db6e5271cee6b3340ebd9d8.001.1","hashtags":["NWS","flood","nwsflashflood","FlashFloodWarning","WIwx"],"entities":[["NWS","ORG"],["#","CARDINAL"],["Flash Flood Warning for","PERSON"],["WI","ORG"],["WI","ORG"],["Iowa","GPE"],["WI","ORG"],["WIwx","PERSON"],["oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.72a97c9be4a284482db6e5271cee6b3340ebd9d8.001.1","PERSON"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","nofollow","tags","noopener"],"cluster":4,"sentiment":-0.2,"topic_id":2,"topic_label":"wi, wiwx, grant, green, iowa"},{"created_at":1752277669011,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/poleshift\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>poleshift<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/polarexcursion\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>polarexcursion<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/earthtilt\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>earthtilt<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/cataclysm\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>cataclysm<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/disaster\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>disaster<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/fire\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>fire<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/tornado\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>tornado<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"poleshiftbot","url":"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/@poleshiftbot\/114837269316042736","clean_content":"#poleshift #polarexcursion #earthtilt #cataclysm #disaster #flood #fire #tornado","hashtags":["poleshift","polarexcursion","earthtilt","cataclysm","disaster","flood","fire","tornado"],"entities":[["#","CARDINAL"],["#","CARDINAL"],["cataclysm","PERSON"],["#","CARDINAL"]],"keywords":["href","tag","hashtag","tags","span"],"cluster":2,"sentiment":0.0,"topic_id":4,"topic_label":"tornado, poleshift, polarexcursion, earthtilt, cataclysm"},{"created_at":1752277471000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/EAS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>EAS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/WEA\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>WEA<\/span><\/a> for Dane, <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/WI\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>WI<\/span><\/a>; <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/Green\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>Green<\/span><\/a>, <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/WI\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>WI<\/span><\/a>; <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/Iowa\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>Iowa<\/span><\/a>, <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/WI\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>WI<\/span><\/a>; <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/Lafayette\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>Lafayette<\/span><\/a>, <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/WI\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>WI<\/span><\/a>: National Weather Service: A FLASH <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FLOOD\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FLOOD<\/span><\/a> WARNING is in effect for this area until 9:45 PM CDT. This is a dangerous and life-threatening situation. Do not attempt to travel unless you are fleeing an area subject to flooding or under an evacuation order. Source: NWS Milwaukee\/Sullivan WI ** DO NOT RELY ON THIS FEED FOR LIFE SAFETY, SEEK OUT OFFICIAL SOURCES ***<\/p>","username":"easwatch","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@easwatch\/114837256347309797","clean_content":"#EAS #WEA for Dane, #WI ; #Green , #WI ; #Iowa , #WI ; #Lafayette , #WI : National Weather Service: A FLASH #FLOOD WARNING is in effect for this area until 9:45 PM CDT. This is a dangerous and life-threatening situation. Do not attempt to travel unless you are fleeing an area subject to flooding or under an evacuation order. Source: NWS Milwaukee\/Sullivan WI ** DO NOT RELY ON THIS FEED FOR LIFE SAFETY, SEEK OUT OFFICIAL SOURCES ***","hashtags":["EAS","WEA","WI","Green","WI","Iowa","WI","Lafayette","WI","FLOOD"],"entities":[["#EAS #","MONEY"],["WEA","ORG"],["WI","PERSON"],["Green","PERSON"],["WI","PERSON"],["Iowa","GPE"],["WI","PERSON"],["Lafayette","PERSON"],["WI","PERSON"],["9:45 PM CDT","TIME"],["Milwaukee","GPE"],["Sullivan WI","PERSON"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","tags","nofollow","dane"],"cluster":1,"sentiment":-0.3222222222,"topic_id":2,"topic_label":"wi, wiwx, grant, green, iowa"},{"created_at":1752277462000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NWS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NWS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/nwsflashflood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>nwsflashflood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FlashFloodWarning\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FlashFloodWarning<\/span><\/a> Flash Flood Warning for Clayton, IA <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/IAwx\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>IAwx<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?id=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.54e6705eadaf7397c22d0144efb048c99c1e0b18.001.1\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.54e6705eadaf7397c22d0144efb048c99c1e0b18.001.1<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"flashflood_bot","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@flashflood_bot\/114837255791460493","clean_content":"#NWS #flood #nwsflashflood #FlashFloodWarning Flash Flood Warning for Clayton, IA #IAwx https:\/\/ alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.54e6705eadaf7397c22d0144efb048c99c1e0b18.001.1","hashtags":["NWS","flood","nwsflashflood","FlashFloodWarning","IAwx"],"entities":[["NWS","ORG"],["#","CARDINAL"],["Flash Flood Warning","PERSON"],["Clayton","PERSON"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","nofollow","tags","noopener"],"cluster":4,"sentiment":0.0,"topic_id":0,"topic_label":"flood, 49, alerts, gov, flashfloodwarning"},{"created_at":1752277458000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NWS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NWS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/nwsflashflood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>nwsflashflood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FlashFloodWarning\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FlashFloodWarning<\/span><\/a> Flash Flood Warning for Des Moines, IA; Henry, IA; Louisa, IA; Muscatine, IA; Henderson, IL; Mercer, IL; Rock Island, IL <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/ILwx\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>ILwx<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?id=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.ff3285ff9db098044ae2cc4033b5cc99e5a395b2.001.1\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.ff3285ff9db098044ae2cc4033b5cc99e5a395b2.001.1<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"flashflood_bot","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@flashflood_bot\/114837255510622640","clean_content":"#NWS #flood #nwsflashflood #FlashFloodWarning Flash Flood Warning for Des Moines, IA; Henry, IA; Louisa, IA; Muscatine, IA; Henderson, IL; Mercer, IL; Rock Island, IL #ILwx https:\/\/ alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.ff3285ff9db098044ae2cc4033b5cc99e5a395b2.001.1","hashtags":["NWS","flood","nwsflashflood","FlashFloodWarning","ILwx"],"entities":[["NWS","ORG"],["#","CARDINAL"],["Flash Flood Warning","PERSON"],["Des Moines","GPE"],["IA","GPE"],["Henry","GPE"],["IA","GPE"],["Louisa","GPE"],["IA","GPE"],["Muscatine","ORG"],["IA","GPE"],["Henderson","GPE"],["IL","ORG"],["Mercer","PERSON"],["IL","ORG"],["Rock Island","GPE"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","nofollow","tags","noopener"],"cluster":4,"sentiment":0.0,"topic_id":0,"topic_label":"flood, 49, alerts, gov, flashfloodwarning"},{"created_at":1752277452000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NWS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NWS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/nwsflashflood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>nwsflashflood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FlashFloodWarning\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FlashFloodWarning<\/span><\/a> Flash Flood Warning for Clinton, IA; Scott, IA; Carroll, IL; Rock Island, IL; Whiteside, IL <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/ILwx\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>ILwx<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?id=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.3de8b29ebdc97f38ca61d5b659741b36b80035e4.001.1\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.3de8b29ebdc97f38ca61d5b659741b36b80035e4.001.1<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"flashflood_bot","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@flashflood_bot\/114837255107218003","clean_content":"#NWS #flood #nwsflashflood #FlashFloodWarning Flash Flood Warning for Clinton, IA; Scott, IA; Carroll, IL; Rock Island, IL; Whiteside, IL #ILwx https:\/\/ alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.3de8b29ebdc97f38ca61d5b659741b36b80035e4.001.1","hashtags":["NWS","flood","nwsflashflood","FlashFloodWarning","ILwx"],"entities":[["NWS","ORG"],["#","CARDINAL"],["Flash Flood Warning","PERSON"],["Clinton","PERSON"],["IA","GPE"],["Scott","ORG"],["IA","GPE"],["Carroll","GPE"],["IL","ORG"],["Rock Island","GPE"],["IL","ORG"],["Whiteside","ORG"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","nofollow","tags","noopener"],"cluster":4,"sentiment":0.0,"topic_id":0,"topic_label":"flood, 49, alerts, gov, flashfloodwarning"},{"created_at":1752277088324,"content":"<p>Experts says there is nothing to worry about on the Axial Seamount because it is underwater. This image is from an underwater volcano in Tonga. <\/p><p><a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/poleshift\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>poleshift<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/polarexcursion\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>polarexcursion<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/earthtilt\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>earthtilt<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/cataclysm\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>cataclysm<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/disaster\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>disaster<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/fire\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>fire<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/tornado\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>tornado<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"poleshiftbot","url":"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/@poleshiftbot\/114837231259631657","clean_content":"Experts says there is nothing to worry about on the Axial Seamount because it is underwater. This image is from an underwater volcano in Tonga. #poleshift #polarexcursion #earthtilt #cataclysm #disaster #flood #fire #tornado","hashtags":["poleshift","polarexcursion","earthtilt","cataclysm","disaster","flood","fire","tornado"],"entities":[["the Axial Seamount","FAC"],["Tonga","GPE"],["#","CARDINAL"],["#","CARDINAL"],["cataclysm","PERSON"],["#","CARDINAL"]],"keywords":["underwater","href","seamount","mastodon","earthtilt"],"cluster":2,"sentiment":0.0,"topic_id":4,"topic_label":"tornado, poleshift, polarexcursion, earthtilt, cataclysm"},{"created_at":1752276969000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NWS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NWS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/nwsflashflood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>nwsflashflood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FlashFloodWarning\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FlashFloodWarning<\/span><\/a> Flash Flood Warning for Grant, WI <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/WIwx\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>WIwx<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?id=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.5e11ea1f922c8ec30439a1e58a809aa48b42d576.001.1\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.5e11ea1f922c8ec30439a1e58a809aa48b42d576.001.1<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"flashflood_bot","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@flashflood_bot\/114837223493589235","clean_content":"#NWS #flood #nwsflashflood #FlashFloodWarning Flash Flood Warning for Grant, WI #WIwx https:\/\/ alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.5e11ea1f922c8ec30439a1e58a809aa48b42d576.001.1","hashtags":["NWS","flood","nwsflashflood","FlashFloodWarning","WIwx"],"entities":[["NWS","ORG"],["#","CARDINAL"],["Flash Flood Warning","PERSON"],["WIwx","PERSON"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","nofollow","tags","noopener"],"cluster":0,"sentiment":0.0,"topic_id":2,"topic_label":"wi, wiwx, grant, green, iowa"},{"created_at":1752276676053,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/watchers.news\/2025\/07\/10\/possible-rare-ball-lightning-captured-camera-alberta-canada\" target=\"_blank\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">watchers.news\/2025\/07\/10\/possi<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">ble-rare-ball-lightning-captured-camera-alberta-canada<\/span><\/a><\/p><p>More and more ball lightning spotted nowadays then ever before. <\/p><p><a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/poleshift\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>poleshift<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/polarexcursion\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>polarexcursion<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/earthtilt\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>earthtilt<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/cataclysm\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>cataclysm<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/disaster\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>disaster<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/fire\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>fire<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/tags\/tornado\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"tag\">#<span>tornado<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"poleshiftbot","url":"https:\/\/mastodon.social\/@poleshiftbot\/114837204241153542","clean_content":"https:\/\/ watchers.news\/2025\/07\/10\/possi ble-rare-ball-lightning-captured-camera-alberta-canada More and more ball lightning spotted nowadays then ever before. #poleshift #polarexcursion #earthtilt #cataclysm #disaster #flood #fire #tornado","hashtags":["poleshift","polarexcursion","earthtilt","cataclysm","disaster","flood","fire","tornado"],"entities":[["watchers.news\/2025\/07\/10\/possi","PERSON"],["#","CARDINAL"],["cataclysm","PERSON"],["#","CARDINAL"]],"keywords":["href","tag","lightning","tags","hashtag"],"cluster":2,"sentiment":0.5,"topic_id":4,"topic_label":"tornado, poleshift, polarexcursion, earthtilt, cataclysm"},{"created_at":1752276496000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NWS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NWS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/nwsflashflood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>nwsflashflood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FlashFloodWarning\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FlashFloodWarning<\/span><\/a> Flash Flood Warning for Grant, WI <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/WIwx\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>WIwx<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?id=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.9a28862fc7fb0c311e926a9578580f1c5b0f4f16.001.1\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.9a28862fc7fb0c311e926a9578580f1c5b0f4f16.001.1<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"flashflood_bot","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@flashflood_bot\/114837192465084974","clean_content":"#NWS #flood #nwsflashflood #FlashFloodWarning Flash Flood Warning for Grant, WI #WIwx https:\/\/ alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.9a28862fc7fb0c311e926a9578580f1c5b0f4f16.001.1","hashtags":["NWS","flood","nwsflashflood","FlashFloodWarning","WIwx"],"entities":[["NWS","ORG"],["#","CARDINAL"],["Flash Flood Warning","PERSON"],["WIwx","PERSON"],["oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.9a28862fc7fb0c311e926a9578580f1c5b0f4f16.001.1","PERSON"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","nofollow","tags","noopener"],"cluster":0,"sentiment":0.0,"topic_id":2,"topic_label":"wi, wiwx, grant, green, iowa"},{"created_at":1752276491000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NWS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NWS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/nwsflashflood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>nwsflashflood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FlashFloodWarning\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FlashFloodWarning<\/span><\/a> Flash Flood Warning for Scott, IA; Rock Island, IL <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/ILwx\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>ILwx<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?id=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.a576938268a1423415f5ddafa12f26c409b7c393.001.1\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.a576938268a1423415f5ddafa12f26c409b7c393.001.1<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"flashflood_bot","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@flashflood_bot\/114837192157031445","clean_content":"#NWS #flood #nwsflashflood #FlashFloodWarning Flash Flood Warning for Scott, IA; Rock Island, IL #ILwx https:\/\/ alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.a576938268a1423415f5ddafa12f26c409b7c393.001.1","hashtags":["NWS","flood","nwsflashflood","FlashFloodWarning","ILwx"],"entities":[["NWS","ORG"],["#","CARDINAL"],["Flash Flood Warning","PERSON"],["Scott","ORG"],["IA","GPE"],["Rock Island","GPE"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","nofollow","tags","noopener"],"cluster":4,"sentiment":0.0,"topic_id":0,"topic_label":"flood, 49, alerts, gov, flashfloodwarning"},{"created_at":1752276492000,"content":"<p>No, weather modification did not cause the deadly flash floods in Texas <a href=\"https:\/\/phys.org\/news\/2025-07-weather-modification-deadly-texas.html\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">phys.org\/news\/2025-07-weather-<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">modification-deadly-texas.html<\/span><\/a><\/p><p><a href=\"https:\/\/veganism.social\/tags\/Texas\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>Texas<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/veganism.social\/tags\/environment\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>environment<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/veganism.social\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/veganism.social\/tags\/floods\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>floods<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/veganism.social\/tags\/flooding\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flooding<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/veganism.social\/tags\/flashflood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flashflood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/veganism.social\/tags\/weather\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>weather<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/veganism.social\/tags\/disinformation\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>disinformation<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"Dragofix","url":"https:\/\/veganism.social\/@Dragofix\/114837192230828164","clean_content":"No, weather modification did not cause the deadly flash floods in Texas https:\/\/ phys.org\/news\/2025-07-weather- modification-deadly-texas.html #Texas #environment #flood #floods #flooding #flashflood #weather #disinformation","hashtags":["Texas","environment","flood","floods","flooding","flashflood","weather","disinformation"],"entities":[["Texas","GPE"],["#","CARDINAL"],["#","CARDINAL"],["#","CARDINAL"]],"keywords":["href","html","floods","flooding","nofollow"],"cluster":0,"sentiment":-0.2,"topic_id":3,"topic_label":"texas, fema, calls, floods, trump"},{"created_at":1752276016000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/EAS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>EAS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/WEA\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>WEA<\/span><\/a> for Scott, <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/IA\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>IA<\/span><\/a>; <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/Rock\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>Rock<\/span><\/a> Island, <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/IL\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>IL<\/span><\/a>: National Weather Service: A FLASH <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FLOOD\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FLOOD<\/span><\/a> EMERGENCY is in effect for this area until 9:00 PM CDT. This is an extremely dangerous and life-threatening situation. Do not attempt to travel unless you are fleeing an area subject to flooding or under an evacuation order. Source: NWS Quad Cities IA IL ** DO NOT RELY ON THIS FEED FOR LIFE SAFETY, SEEK OUT OFFICIAL SOURCES ***<\/p>","username":"easwatch","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@easwatch\/114837161036718027","clean_content":"#EAS #WEA for Scott, #IA ; #Rock Island, #IL : National Weather Service: A FLASH #FLOOD EMERGENCY is in effect for this area until 9:00 PM CDT. This is an extremely dangerous and life-threatening situation. Do not attempt to travel unless you are fleeing an area subject to flooding or under an evacuation order. Source: NWS Quad Cities IA IL ** DO NOT RELY ON THIS FEED FOR LIFE SAFETY, SEEK OUT OFFICIAL SOURCES ***","hashtags":["EAS","WEA","IA","Rock","IL","FLOOD"],"entities":[["#EAS #","MONEY"],["WEA","ORG"],["Scott","ORG"],["IA","GPE"],["Rock Island","PERSON"],["IL","PERSON"],["9:00 PM CDT","TIME"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","tags","nofollow","scott"],"cluster":1,"sentiment":-0.3833333333,"topic_id":1,"topic_label":"il, ia, life, area, feed"},{"created_at":1752276012000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NWS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NWS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/nwsflashflood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>nwsflashflood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FlashFloodWarning\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FlashFloodWarning<\/span><\/a> Flash Flood Warning for Colfax, NM <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NMwx\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NMwx<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?id=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.019d514bbc58f237bc28b70c04adf062610f20b4.001.1\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.019d514bbc58f237bc28b70c04adf062610f20b4.001.1<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"flashflood_bot","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@flashflood_bot\/114837160745845080","clean_content":"#NWS #flood #nwsflashflood #FlashFloodWarning Flash Flood Warning for Colfax, NM #NMwx https:\/\/ alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.019d514bbc58f237bc28b70c04adf062610f20b4.001.1","hashtags":["NWS","flood","nwsflashflood","FlashFloodWarning","NMwx"],"entities":[["NWS","ORG"],["#","CARDINAL"],["Flash Flood Warning for","PERSON"],["NMwx","PERSON"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","nofollow","tags","noopener"],"cluster":0,"sentiment":0.0,"topic_id":0,"topic_label":"flood, 49, alerts, gov, flashfloodwarning"},{"created_at":1752275534000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NWS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NWS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/nwsflashflood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>nwsflashflood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FlashFloodWarning\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FlashFloodWarning<\/span><\/a> Flash Flood Warning for Hampshire, MA <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/MAwx\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>MAwx<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?id=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.faa3576cdc5f6df289ff751b28501d58f933acb5.002.1\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.faa3576cdc5f6df289ff751b28501d58f933acb5.002.1<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"flashflood_bot","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@flashflood_bot\/114837129433008797","clean_content":"#NWS #flood #nwsflashflood #FlashFloodWarning Flash Flood Warning for Hampshire, MA #MAwx https:\/\/ alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.faa3576cdc5f6df289ff751b28501d58f933acb5.002.1","hashtags":["NWS","flood","nwsflashflood","FlashFloodWarning","MAwx"],"entities":[["NWS","ORG"],["#","CARDINAL"],["Flash Flood Warning","PERSON"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","nofollow","tags","noopener"],"cluster":0,"sentiment":0.0,"topic_id":0,"topic_label":"flood, 49, alerts, gov, flashfloodwarning"},{"created_at":1752274582000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NWS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NWS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/nwsflashflood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>nwsflashflood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FlashFloodWarning\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FlashFloodWarning<\/span><\/a> Flash Flood Warning for Clayton, GA; DeKalb, GA; Fulton, GA; Henry, GA <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/GAwx\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>GAwx<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?id=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.cad598209428303232789cb397ffe1cc8af66754.001.1\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.cad598209428303232789cb397ffe1cc8af66754.001.1<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"flashflood_bot","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@flashflood_bot\/114837067027423564","clean_content":"#NWS #flood #nwsflashflood #FlashFloodWarning Flash Flood Warning for Clayton, GA; DeKalb, GA; Fulton, GA; Henry, GA #GAwx https:\/\/ alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.cad598209428303232789cb397ffe1cc8af66754.001.1","hashtags":["NWS","flood","nwsflashflood","FlashFloodWarning","GAwx"],"entities":[["NWS","ORG"],["#","CARDINAL"],["Flash Flood Warning","PERSON"],["Clayton","GPE"],["GA","ORG"],["DeKalb","GPE"],["GA","ORG"],["Fulton","GPE"],["GA","ORG"],["Henry","GPE"],["GAwx","PERSON"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","nofollow","tags","noopener"],"cluster":0,"sentiment":0.0,"topic_id":0,"topic_label":"flood, 49, alerts, gov, flashfloodwarning"},{"created_at":1752274576000,"content":"<p><a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/NWS\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>NWS<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/flood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>flood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/nwsflashflood\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>nwsflashflood<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/FlashFloodWarning\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>FlashFloodWarning<\/span><\/a> Flash Flood Warning for Dubuque, IA <a href=\"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/tags\/IAwx\" class=\"mention hashtag\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" target=\"_blank\">#<span>IAwx<\/span><\/a> <a href=\"https:\/\/alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?id=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.3fa8c2a98d1bea2e725d425842b8bb4bf2344c84.001.1\" rel=\"nofollow noopener\" translate=\"no\" target=\"_blank\"><span class=\"invisible\">https:\/\/<\/span><span class=\"ellipsis\">alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i<\/span><span class=\"invisible\">d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.3fa8c2a98d1bea2e725d425842b8bb4bf2344c84.001.1<\/span><\/a><\/p>","username":"flashflood_bot","url":"https:\/\/m.ai6yr.org\/@flashflood_bot\/114837066660929064","clean_content":"#NWS #flood #nwsflashflood #FlashFloodWarning Flash Flood Warning for Dubuque, IA #IAwx https:\/\/ alerts-v2.weather.gov\/search?i d=urn:oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.3fa8c2a98d1bea2e725d425842b8bb4bf2344c84.001.1","hashtags":["NWS","flood","nwsflashflood","FlashFloodWarning","IAwx"],"entities":[["NWS","ORG"],["#","CARDINAL"],["Flash Flood Warning for","PERSON"],["oid:2.49.0.1.840.0.3fa8c2a98d1bea2e725d425842b8bb4bf2344c84.001.1","PERSON"]],"keywords":["href","hashtag","nofollow","tags","noopener"],"cluster":4,"sentiment":0.0,"topic_id":0,"topic_label":"flood, 49, alerts, gov, flashfloodwarning"}]